- How are you?
- I'm fine.
- From where?
- From South Africa.
What did you hear me say?
That my faith shouldn't be based on the improvement after prayer.
Your faith should not be based on the improvement.
What should your faith be based on?
I should be patient. If God does not answer, it doesn't mean that it is no.
It means He is waiting for the right time.
Clap for her.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Before now, how have you been living your Christian life when it comes to prayer?
I've been praying but sometimes when I see things don't come my way, I lose hope.
But this time?
But this time, because of your message, I will be strong.
You are healed already.
Yes, sir.
You have received Jesus; you are healed to heal others.
Touch your leg.
The other one.
Healing In Jesus' Name
I'm not there; I'm here.
Here I am; I'm not there.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
What happened?
[Power of God.]
I said, "What happened?"
Ah - power happened.
I said, "What happened?". You said, "Power!" What is power?
The SCOAN Sunday Service
That is all. This is what we've been talking about.
This is just it.
What happened is that Jesus immediately came to the scene.
Healed In Jesus' Name
What happened?
Jesus immediately came to the scene.
Thank You, Jesus! I can walk now!
Healed In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus! I can walk now! I am healed!
TESTIMONY TIME
My name is Lerato Motsoari from South Africa.
I had a problem of lymphedema.
That is, the circulation was not okay in my feet so it caused a blockade down there.
You would see a lot of water not flowing the correct way.
I couldn't walk for a long distance and I couldn't stand for long.
I would feel pains and discomfort.
That really caused a lot of problems.
Even when I wanted to buy shoes, I would struggle to find them in the right size.
My self-esteem was low. I'm a teacher.
When the learners were looking at me when I was wearing a skirt,
I would feel uncomfortable because they could see that my feet were not equal.
One foot was too big and the other one was little.
You mean the problem affected your teaching career.
Yes, I had to stand for long and standing was a problem because of pains.
On Sunday, I came; I was sittng over there.
The man of God came and said, I should touch my feet.
I did that. I don't really know what happened after that.
I asked people, "Did the man of God pray for me?"
They said, "No, he didn't pray for you".
I don't really know what happened.
You mean you cannot explain what happened to you after the Prophet had asked you to touch your legs?
No, I can't really.
I can walk without any discomfort.
I don't feel any pains now.
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus!
This one, I could not tap it like this.
I would start feeling a lot of pains.
It would tell me that I had walked too much or tapped it a lot.
So, I would feel discomfort.
If I walked a lot like a long distance, my feet would swell up
and the discomfort would come again.
But now, are you feeling any pains?
I'm feeling okay; I can twist it like that.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus!
This is how my feet used to look like - they were big.
But now, they are no longer big.
I used to struggle to find the right shoe size.
When I wanted to buy new shoes, I would have to check the ones that are comfortable
because immediately when my feet swelled up, I would feel the pain too much.
But now, I believe I can buy any type of shoes.
Hallelujah. Let's put our hands together for Jesus!
Jesus Christ is still the Healer. We have to believe in Him. That's all.
You are healed by Christ's Word. You should go and live by that Word.
Make God's Word the standard for your life
so that the healing and deliverance that God has given you
will remain permanent in your life, in Jesus' name.
Amen.